Hello friends, welcome to National Certification.
If you are new to this channel, then
like the channel, subscribe and click
on the bell button. If you
like the video, then definitely like it.
Friends, let's talk about General
Insurance Corporation of India Limited.
Friends, this code is a recommendation for you.
Giving 13 recommendations is the
work of registered people. I want to give you information about stocks.
I have
made a video of Godrej Agrovet. That
video can also be seen on my channel
and
its link is also given in the description box of this video. So, do
watch that video. Very important.
After this, one more thing, before doing it, my friend
asked me a question that if it is
possible to do business in the stock market without stocks, then
I
answered him with a very important question. Wherever you want to work, then
select that and
chant a good Kalpana Yadav and we have to do our work in trading stocks.
No, no stop, only a laptop
and internet connection is required.
Why not, friends, it is not
that easy. There is no
shortcut in this world like this and
especially by doing this.  For people like us,
before leaving your job, you should ask yourself some
questions. Friends, the first question
I have asked, they will check
whether you have the education or knowledge of the stock market. Do you have any knowledge
or experience in it? If you don't have any, then
take it and plug it in on
Thursday or by browsing the internet,
you can gain knowledge and for that you have to
give time. The second thing is that you have a
good trading meter. Have you done stupid
trading
or paper trading? It does
not mean that you will be good at ragging. It does not mean that trading, stock
trading, policy and it is
always Rafale, it is very last. The
second thing is that you should have an emergency
subscription. If
you
can come into the market through subscription and if
you want to take a full plunge in it, then you should have an
emergency
subscription and that is why you should have Amazon. The
thing that Himesh has said is, do you
know that you will not always be successful in trading,
but are you emotionally prepared for it?
After leaving the job,
whatever profit and loss you have on your trading will depend on
that and
for trading  If you have taken the decision to leave that job,
you should be emotionally prepared before taking it
because whatever profit you want, it
depends on your trading and testing
that you have to choose the right option for you. There are
many options in the stock market,
investment trading and
this phone, currency market etc. The
biggest question is that you choose the right option for you.
If you fit in these five questions
or if you get it right in these questions, then
you can definitely leave and
work in the stock market full time. This is a
little risk, so understand this and take
your video
that if you are running a company, Corporation of India, then we will
see its chart pattern.
Friends, in a month we will see the pattern of the company formed for 14 years.
Then Shyam
subscribe
and
subscribe. This is the company history through 2018.
So subscribe and the chat
starts automatically. If you want to go then do
not go at all.
Subscribe to this
channel friends.
Now we will see its sector. So from the
sectors, see friends, then
sector-69 finance investment, so in this
123 456 subscribe and from the market, the
strong market capital
subscribe companies some
time ago  We will invest in it, their zone
president
profit and loss company
now in 2019 company -
company has more than 100
profit
subscribe has profit up plus I will
come then we will think in it whether to invest
or not right now we will not
go into it at all, otherwise okay now we will
see the share holding pattern of the company, so
look at the share holding pattern friends, who has the power,
that too President of
India, so this weight company government company
subscribe is
with the Indian Government of India, so after a
little after this
subscribe and
like you
click on the subscribe button subscribe
subscribe
balance
subscribe to
124, let's
see by doing this illegal occupation, so
till tomorrow on how many companies have returned, I have
not done anything company company satta company
appointed
subscribe
company
[Music]
sure
subscribe if you
want 10 companies then
subscribe like and
subscribe to the channel